<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opinion on Mr. Eric</title>
    <link>http://mreric.org/tags/opinion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Opinion on Mr. Eric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>english</language>
    <copyright>Welcome to study, discuss, even debate together. &lt;br /&gt;No plagiarism please, because simply copying, even only one word, even only one minute, will waste time in our life. While copying, you use other’s opinions, but yourself don’t have one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons license&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;https://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-nc-sa/4.0/88x31.png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This work is licensed under the&lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International (CC BY-NC-SA 4.0) &lt;/a&gt;License Agreement.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:09:36 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mreric.org/tags/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>‘A Long Walk To Water’ Reading Reflection (G5)</title>
      <link>http://mreric.org/posts/essayalongwalktowater/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:09:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mreric.org/posts/essayalongwalktowater/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;‘A Long Walk To Water’ is a story about two main characters, one Salva, one Nya. Salva experienced war and Nya met negative effects on life for the drought of Sudan. Salva got a new family in the US but also had some members of his original family. He cherished any chance he met and dug wells for people of Sudan, even his enemies, which included Nya. I agree with what he said: Never Lose Hope.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biography about Nikola Tesla (G4)</title>
      <link>http://mreric.org/posts/essaytesla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:31:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mreric.org/posts/essaytesla/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Who invented the world’s first hydroelectric power plant? Who invented x-rays? Who invented the neon lights? If you search on the internet, the true inventor’s name will never come out. Who is it then? It’s Nikola Tesla, a DETERMINED GENIUS! He invented all of these things, and many more useful things! Still, because Tesla has disagreements with Edison, a famous inventor, and people believe that famous people are always right, Tesla was brought no fame, but he deserved slightly more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh the places you&#39;ll go!</title>
      <link>http://mreric.org/posts/ohtheplacesyoullgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 19:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mreric.org/posts/ohtheplacesyoullgo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I loved Dr.Seuss’s books. And when I searched for his POEM, I found one that I had already read about:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways To Express Yourself (G4)</title>
      <link>http://mreric.org/posts/essaywaystoexpressyourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 13:31:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mreric.org/posts/essaywaystoexpressyourself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are MANY ways to express ourselves. You must know one, that is, chatting. You use words to express your self while chatting. But what if you can’t express yourself through words? There are also many ways to express yourself. In this text I’ll tell you about two ways: Drama, and Music. And it’s all my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer or not (G4)</title>
      <link>http://mreric.org/posts/essayvolunteerornot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 14:30:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mreric.org/posts/essayvolunteerornot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever volunteered before? If you haven’t, then you should try your best to volunteer more. However, you don’t need to volunteer because everyone has their civil rights, which don’t force you to volunteer. Therefore you could not do it if you can’t, or don’t want to do it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should We Reach Out (G4)</title>
      <link>http://mreric.org/posts/essayshouldwereachingout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 14:30:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mreric.org/posts/essayshouldwereachingout/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Had you ever met a homeless person? Did you decide to help them of not? However, it’s important to help them anyway you could, normal people should, and could help the homeless. but if he don’t needs help, you could leave him alone for some time. There might be someone which could help him! Here’s a story:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
