<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reflection on Mr. Eric</title>
    <link>https://mreric.org/tags/reflection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reflection on Mr. Eric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>english</language>
    <copyright>Welcome to study, discuss, even debate together. &lt;br /&gt;No plagiarism please, because simply copying, even only one word, even only one minute, will waste time in our life. While copying, you use other’s opinions, but yourself don’t have one. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons license&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;https://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-nc-sa/4.0/88x31.png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This work is licensed under the&lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International (CC BY-NC-SA 4.0) &lt;/a&gt;License Agreement.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 13:31:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mreric.org/tags/reflection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dehumanization of slaves</title>
      <link>https://mreric.org/posts/essaychains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 13:31:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mreric.org/posts/essaychains/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Chains&amp;rsquo; is a novel by Laurie Halse Anderson, and the book mainly talks about the experiences of a black girl slave in first person. This book occurs quite a long time ago, when the American War for Independence had just started and slaves were treated very badly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘A Long Walk To Water’ Reading Reflection (G5)</title>
      <link>https://mreric.org/posts/essayalongwalktowater/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:09:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mreric.org/posts/essayalongwalktowater/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;‘A Long Walk To Water’ is a story about two main characters, one Salva, one Nya. Salva experienced war and Nya met negative effects on life for the drought of Sudan. Salva got a new family in the US but also had some members of his original family. He cherished any chance he met and dug wells for people of Sudan, even his enemies, which included Nya. I agree with what he said: Never Lose Hope.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
